JAMES ROGERS

UI / Graphic Design

Web Development

Front-End Development Product Design

jamesrogers.io – napacreativeco.com 707.365.3802 hello@napacreativeco.com

About Me

I'm a 32 year old Front End Developer and Graphic Designer based in Napa, California. I focus my time on creating Websites and Graphics for friends, bands, brands, and small businesses. On my free time I like to produce music, read and practice illustration.

Skills

Photoshop Figma HTML

Illustrator WordPress CSS / SCSS

AfterEffects React JavaScript / jQuery

Premiere Gatsby PHP

Experience

Lead Developer, Designer

Napa Creative Company

Napa, California 03.2020 – Present Projects range from Merchandise design, Web Design, Web Development, Logo Design, Packaging Design, Menu design, Product Photography, and more.

Sr. Graphic Designer

Gaby Inc.

Sebastopol, California 01.2019 – 03.2020 I was responsible for Designing and Developing new Websites for a collection of companies within our 'House of Brands'. Other projects include Packaging design, Trade show design, Menu design and many more.

Lead Designer

Sonoma Pacific Dist.

Santa Rosa, California 11.2016 – 12.2018 My responsibilities ranged from Web Design and Development, in-house and as a service to our brands, Packaging design, Trade show design, Compliance review, and more.

Education

Code Academy Completed courses on JavaScript, Ruby,

PHP, Python and SQL.

Udemy Completed multiple courses on JavaScript &

ES6, React with and without Redux, Front-End Web Development, Full Stack

Development, Swift and more.

Skillshare Completed courses on Graphic Design

fundamentals, Typography, AfterEffects, Photo Editing and Facebook Advertising.

High school Diploma Forest Charter School, Class of 2007,

Truckee, California